{"All_data": {"2002": {"BEL": {"country": "Belgie", "year": "2002", "humanity": "4.8", "justiceSystem": "4.4", "police": "5.6", "politicians": "4.3", "parliament": "5.0", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.9", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "BEL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "BGR": {"country": "Bulgarije", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "BGR", "fillKey": "none"}, "CYP": {"country": "Cyprus", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CYP", "fillKey": "none"}, "DNK": {"country": "Denemarken", "year": "2002", "humanity": "7.0", "justiceSystem": "7.1", "police": "7.9", "politicians": "5.5", "parliament": "6.2", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "6.5", "ISO": "DNK", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "DEU": {"country": "Duitsland", "year": "2002", "humanity": "4.7", "justiceSystem": "5.7", "police": "6.7", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.5", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.5", "un": "5.2", "ISO": "DEU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "EST": {"country": "Estland", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "EST", "fillKey": "none"}, "FIN": {"country": "Finland", "year": "2002", "humanity": "6.5", "justiceSystem": "6.8", "police": "8.0", "politicians": "4.8", "parliament": "5.8", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.9", "un": "6.5", "ISO": "FIN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "FRA": {"country": "Frankrijk", "year": "2002", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "4.8", "police": "5.9", "politicians": "3.7", "parliament": "4.5", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.4", "un": "4.6", "ISO": "FRA", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GRC": {"country": "Griekenland", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "GRC", "fillKey": "none"}, "HUN": {"country": "Hongarije", "year": "2002", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "5.1", "police": "4.9", "politicians": "3.9", "parliament": "5.0", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "5.7", "un": "6.0", "ISO": "HUN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "IRL": {"country": "Ierland", "year": "2002", "humanity": "5.5", "justiceSystem": "5.1", "police": "6.5", "politicians": "3.7", "parliament": "4.4", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "5.7", "ISO": "IRL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ISL": {"country": "IJsland", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "ISL", "fillKey": "none"}, "ITA": {"country": "Italie", "year": "2002", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "ITA", "fillKey": "none"}, "XKX": {"country": "Kosovo", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "XKX", "fillKey": "none"}, "HRV": {"country": "Kroatie", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "HRV", "fillKey": "none"}, "LTU": {"country": "Litouwen", "year": "2002", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "LTU", "fillKey": "none"}, "NLD": {"country": "Nederland", "year": "2002", "humanity": "5.7", "justiceSystem": "5.4", "police": "5.8", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "5.2", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "NLD", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "NOR": {"country": "Noorwegen", "year": "2002", "humanity": "6.6", "justiceSystem": "6.3", "police": "7.0", "politicians": "4.6", "parliament": "5.7", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "6.8", "ISO": "NOR", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "UKR": {"country": "Oekraine", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "UKR", "fillKey": "none"}, "AUT": {"country": "Oostenrijk", "year": "2002", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "6.1", "police": "6.4", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "5.1", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.2", "un": "4.5", "ISO": "AUT", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "POL": {"country": "Polen", "year": "2002", "humanity": "3.7", "justiceSystem": "3.7", "police": "4.9", "politicians": "2.7", "parliament": "3.5", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.6", "ISO": "POL", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "PRT": {"country": "Portugal", "year": "2002", "humanity": "4.2", "justiceSystem": "4.3", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.8", "parliament": "4.4", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "PRT", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SVN": {"country": "Slovenie", "year": "2002", "humanity": "4.0", "justiceSystem": "4.3", "police": "4.9", "politicians": "3.1", "parliament": "4.0", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "SVN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SVK": {"country": "Slowakije", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "SVK", "fillKey": "none"}, "ESP": {"country": "Spanje", "year": "2002", "humanity": "4.9", "justiceSystem": "4.3", "police": "5.4", "politicians": "3.4", "parliament": "4.8", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "ESP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "CZE": {"country": "Tsjechie", "year": "2002", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CZE", "fillKey": "none"}, "GBR": {"country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "year": "2002", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "5.0", "police": "6.0", "politicians": "3.8", "parliament": "4.7", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "3.6", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "GBR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SWE": {"country": "Zweden", "year": "2002", "humanity": "6.1", "justiceSystem": "6.1", "police": "6.8", "politicians": "4.7", "parliament": "5.9", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "6.6", "ISO": "SWE", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "CHE": {"country": "Zwitserland", "year": "2002", "humanity": "5.6", "justiceSystem": "6.2", "police": "6.8", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "5.8", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "CHE", "fillKey": "4-6"}}, "2004": {"BEL": {"country": "Belgie", "year": "2004", "humanity": "4.8", "justiceSystem": "4.8", "police": "5.8", "politicians": "4.2", "parliament": "4.7", "politicalParties": "4.3", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "BEL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "BGR": {"country": "Bulgarije", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "BGR", "fillKey": "none"}, "CYP": {"country": "Cyprus", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CYP", "fillKey": "none"}, "DNK": {"country": "Denemarken", "year": "2004", "humanity": "6.8", "justiceSystem": "7.2", "police": "7.9", "politicians": "5.6", "parliament": "6.3", "politicalParties": "5.6", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "6.6", "ISO": "DNK", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "DEU": {"country": "Duitsland", "year": "2004", "humanity": "4.8", "justiceSystem": "5.5", "police": "6.5", "politicians": "3.2", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "3.2", "europeanParliament": "4.2", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "DEU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "EST": {"country": "Estland", "year": "2004", "humanity": "5.2", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "5.7", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "3.1", "europeanParliament": "4.9", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "EST", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "FIN": {"country": "Finland", "year": "2004", "humanity": "6.5", "justiceSystem": "6.9", "police": "8.0", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "6.0", "politicalParties": "5.0", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.6", "ISO": "FIN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "FRA": {"country": "Frankrijk", "year": "2004", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "4.8", "police": "5.8", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "FRA", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GRC": {"country": "Griekenland", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "GRC", "fillKey": "none"}, "HUN": {"country": "Hongarije", "year": "2004", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "4.4", "police": "5.2", "politicians": "2.7", "parliament": "3.6", "politicalParties": "2.7", "europeanParliament": "5.2", "un": "5.7", "ISO": "HUN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "IRL": {"country": "Ierland", "year": "2004", "humanity": "5.8", "justiceSystem": "5.2", "police": "6.6", "politicians": "3.9", "parliament": "4.7", "politicalParties": "4.0", "europeanParliament": "5.4", "un": "5.8", "ISO": "IRL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ISL": {"country": "IJsland", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "ISL", "fillKey": "none"}, "ITA": {"country": "Italie", "year": "2004", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "ITA", "fillKey": "none"}, "XKX": {"country": "Kosovo", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "XKX", "fillKey": "none"}, "HRV": {"country": "Kroatie", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "HRV", "fillKey": "none"}, "LTU": {"country": "Litouwen", "year": "2004", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "LTU", "fillKey": "none"}, "NLD": {"country": "Nederland", "year": "2004", "humanity": "5.8", "justiceSystem": "5.5", "police": "6.0", "politicians": "4.7", "parliament": "4.7", "politicalParties": "4.8", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "NLD", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "NOR": {"country": "Noorwegen", "year": "2004", "humanity": "6.6", "justiceSystem": "6.4", "police": "7.1", "politicians": "4.2", "parliament": "5.4", "politicalParties": "4.3", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "6.9", "ISO": "NOR", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "UKR": {"country": "Oekraine", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "UKR", "fillKey": "none"}, "AUT": {"country": "Oostenrijk", "year": "2004", "humanity": "5.2", "justiceSystem": "5.8", "police": "6.2", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "4.8", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "4.5", "ISO": "AUT", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "POL": {"country": "Polen", "year": "2004", "humanity": "3.6", "justiceSystem": "3.0", "police": "4.6", "politicians": "1.9", "parliament": "2.4", "politicalParties": "1.9", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "POL", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "PRT": {"country": "Portugal", "year": "2004", "humanity": "3.9", "justiceSystem": "3.9", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.1", "parliament": "3.7", "politicalParties": "2.1", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "PRT", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "SVN": {"country": "Slovenie", "year": "2004", "humanity": "6.1", "justiceSystem": "5.8", "police": "6.5", "politicians": "4.2", "parliament": "5.4", "politicalParties": "4.4", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "6.3", "ISO": "SVN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "SVK": {"country": "Slowakije", "year": "2004", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "3.8", "police": "4.7", "politicians": "3.1", "parliament": "4.1", "politicalParties": "3.2", "europeanParliament": "4.5", "un": "4.6", "ISO": "SVK", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ESP": {"country": "Spanje", "year": "2004", "humanity": "4.9", "justiceSystem": "4.7", "police": "5.9", "politicians": "3.7", "parliament": "5.1", "politicalParties": "3.7", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "ESP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "CZE": {"country": "Tsjechie", "year": "2004", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CZE", "fillKey": "none"}, "GBR": {"country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "year": "2004", "humanity": "5.2", "justiceSystem": "5.1", "police": "6.1", "politicians": "3.6", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "3.7", "europeanParliament": "3.5", "un": "5.2", "ISO": "GBR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SWE": {"country": "Zweden", "year": "2004", "humanity": "6.1", "justiceSystem": "5.8", "police": "6.5", "politicians": "4.2", "parliament": "5.4", "politicalParties": "4.4", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "6.3", "ISO": "SWE", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "CHE": {"country": "Zwitserland", "year": "2004", "humanity": "5.7", "justiceSystem": "6.1", "police": "6.9", "politicians": "4.8", "parliament": "5.5", "politicalParties": "4.6", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "CHE", "fillKey": "4-6"}}, "2006": {"BEL": {"country": "Belgie", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.0", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "5.9", "politicians": "4.4", "parliament": "5.0", "politicalParties": "4.4", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "BEL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "BGR": {"country": "Bulgarije", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "BGR", "fillKey": "none"}, "CYP": {"country": "Cyprus", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CYP", "fillKey": "none"}, "DNK": {"country": "Denemarken", "year": "2006", "humanity": "7.0", "justiceSystem": "7.5", "police": "7.8", "politicians": "5.6", "parliament": "6.4", "politicalParties": "4.8", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "DNK", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "DEU": {"country": "Duitsland", "year": "2006", "humanity": "4.8", "justiceSystem": "5.6", "police": "6.6", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "3.3", "europeanParliament": "4.1", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "DEU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "EST": {"country": "Estland", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.3", "justiceSystem": "5.1", "police": "5.5", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.6", "politicalParties": "5.7", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.5", "ISO": "EST", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "FIN": {"country": "Finland", "year": "2006", "humanity": "6.6", "justiceSystem": "7.0", "police": "8.0", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "6.0", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "5.3", "un": "5.6", "ISO": "FIN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "FRA": {"country": "Frankrijk", "year": "2006", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "5.7", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "FRA", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GRC": {"country": "Griekenland", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "GRC", "fillKey": "none"}, "HUN": {"country": "Hongarije", "year": "2006", "humanity": "4.3", "justiceSystem": "4.3", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.5", "parliament": "3.4", "politicalParties": "5.0", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.5", "ISO": "HUN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "IRL": {"country": "Ierland", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.4", "justiceSystem": "5.0", "police": "6.1", "politicians": "3.8", "parliament": "4.8", "politicalParties": "3.2", "europeanParliament": "4.4", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "IRL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ISL": {"country": "IJsland", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "ISL", "fillKey": "none"}, "ITA": {"country": "Italie", "year": "2006", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "ITA", "fillKey": "none"}, "XKX": {"country": "Kosovo", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "XKX", "fillKey": "none"}, "HRV": {"country": "Kroatie", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "HRV", "fillKey": "none"}, "LTU": {"country": "Litouwen", "year": "2006", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "LTU", "fillKey": "none"}, "NLD": {"country": "Nederland", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.8", "justiceSystem": "5.8", "police": "6.2", "politicians": "5.0", "parliament": "5.3", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "3.5", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "NLD", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "NOR": {"country": "Noorwegen", "year": "2006", "humanity": "6.8", "justiceSystem": "6.6", "police": "7.2", "politicians": "4.4", "parliament": "5.7", "politicalParties": "2.6", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "NOR", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "UKR": {"country": "Oekraine", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "UKR", "fillKey": "none"}, "AUT": {"country": "Oostenrijk", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "6.0", "police": "6.3", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "4.9", "politicalParties": "3.3", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "AUT", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "POL": {"country": "Polen", "year": "2006", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "3.8", "police": "5.0", "politicians": "2.1", "parliament": "2.7", "politicalParties": "3.9", "europeanParliament": "5.3", "un": "5.7", "ISO": "POL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "PRT": {"country": "Portugal", "year": "2006", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "4.0", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.5", "parliament": "3.8", "politicalParties": "5.1", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "PRT", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SVN": {"country": "Slovenie", "year": "2006", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "4.2", "police": "5.0", "politicians": "3.2", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "4.5", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "6.8", "ISO": "SVN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SVK": {"country": "Slowakije", "year": "2006", "humanity": "4.3", "justiceSystem": "4.2", "police": "4.7", "politicians": "3.6", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "2.1", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "SVK", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ESP": {"country": "Spanje", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "5.0", "police": "6.0", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "5.0", "politicalParties": "2.5", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "ESP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "CZE": {"country": "Tsjechie", "year": "2006", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CZE", "fillKey": "none"}, "GBR": {"country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.4", "justiceSystem": "5.0", "police": "6.0", "politicians": "3.4", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "4.6", "europeanParliament": "4.5", "un": "6.4", "ISO": "GBR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SWE": {"country": "Zweden", "year": "2006", "humanity": "6.3", "justiceSystem": "6.0", "police": "6.5", "politicians": "4.5", "parliament": "5.6", "politicalParties": "3.2", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "SWE", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "CHE": {"country": "Zwitserland", "year": "2006", "humanity": "5.7", "justiceSystem": "6.2", "police": "6.9", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "5.8", "politicalParties": "3.6", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "CHE", "fillKey": "4-6"}}, "2008": {"BEL": {"country": "Belgie", "year": "2008", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "6.0", "politicians": "4.0", "parliament": "4.6", "politicalParties": "4.0", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "BEL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "BGR": {"country": "Bulgarije", "year": "2008", "humanity": "3.5", "justiceSystem": "2.3", "police": "3.3", "politicians": "1.6", "parliament": "1.9", "politicalParties": "1.7", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "4.8", "ISO": "BGR", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "CYP": {"country": "Cyprus", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "6.4", "police": "5.9", "politicians": "4.5", "parliament": "5.6", "politicalParties": "4.4", "europeanParliament": "6.0", "un": "4.8", "ISO": "CYP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "DNK": {"country": "Denemarken", "year": "2008", "humanity": "6.9", "justiceSystem": "7.3", "police": "7.6", "politicians": "5.6", "parliament": "6.5", "politicalParties": "5.7", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.5", "ISO": "DNK", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "DEU": {"country": "Duitsland", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.9", "justiceSystem": "5.8", "police": "6.8", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.7", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "DEU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "EST": {"country": "Estland", "year": "2008", "humanity": "3.5", "justiceSystem": "2.3", "police": "3.3", "politicians": "1.6", "parliament": "1.9", "politicalParties": "1.7", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "4.8", "ISO": "EST", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "FIN": {"country": "Finland", "year": "2008", "humanity": "6.4", "justiceSystem": "7.1", "police": "8.0", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "6.0", "politicalParties": "5.0", "europeanParliament": "5.2", "un": "6.7", "ISO": "FIN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "FRA": {"country": "Frankrijk", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "5.1", "police": "5.8", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.5", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "FRA", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GRC": {"country": "Griekenland", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "GRC", "fillKey": "none"}, "HUN": {"country": "Hongarije", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "3.7", "police": "4.3", "politicians": "1.9", "parliament": "2.6", "politicalParties": "2.0", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "4.5", "ISO": "HUN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "IRL": {"country": "Ierland", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "IRL", "fillKey": "none"}, "ISL": {"country": "IJsland", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "ISL", "fillKey": "none"}, "ITA": {"country": "Italie", "year": "2008", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "ITA", "fillKey": "none"}, "XKX": {"country": "Kosovo", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "XKX", "fillKey": "none"}, "HRV": {"country": "Kroatie", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "HRV", "fillKey": "none"}, "LTU": {"country": "Litouwen", "year": "2008", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "LTU", "fillKey": "none"}, "NLD": {"country": "Nederland", "year": "2008", "humanity": "6.0", "justiceSystem": "5.9", "police": "6.3", "politicians": "5.2", "parliament": "5.6", "politicalParties": "5.2", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "5.6", "ISO": "NLD", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "NOR": {"country": "Noorwegen", "year": "2008", "humanity": "6.6", "justiceSystem": "6.8", "police": "7.0", "politicians": "4.6", "parliament": "5.8", "politicalParties": "4.8", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.8", "ISO": "NOR", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "UKR": {"country": "Oekraine", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "UKR", "fillKey": "none"}, "AUT": {"country": "Oostenrijk", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "AUT", "fillKey": "none"}, "POL": {"country": "Polen", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "3.9", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.3", "parliament": "3.0", "politicalParties": "2.3", "europeanParliament": "4.5", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "POL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "PRT": {"country": "Portugal", "year": "2008", "humanity": "3.7", "justiceSystem": "3.8", "police": "5.3", "politicians": "2.3", "parliament": "3.5", "politicalParties": "2.4", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "PRT", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "SVN": {"country": "Slovenie", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.3", "justiceSystem": "4.3", "police": "5.0", "politicians": "3.4", "parliament": "4.4", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "SVN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SVK": {"country": "Slowakije", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "4.1", "police": "4.8", "politicians": "3.6", "parliament": "4.0", "politicalParties": "3.6", "europeanParliament": "5.2", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "SVK", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ESP": {"country": "Spanje", "year": "2008", "humanity": "4.9", "justiceSystem": "4.3", "police": "6.1", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "5.0", "politicalParties": "3.2", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "ESP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "CZE": {"country": "Tsjechie", "year": "2008", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CZE", "fillKey": "none"}, "GBR": {"country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "year": "2008", "humanity": "5.3", "justiceSystem": "5.2", "police": "6.2", "politicians": "3.6", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "3.6", "europeanParliament": "3.6", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "GBR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SWE": {"country": "Zweden", "year": "2008", "humanity": "6.4", "justiceSystem": "6.1", "police": "6.6", "politicians": "4.6", "parliament": "5.7", "politicalParties": "4.8", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "6.4", "ISO": "SWE", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "CHE": {"country": "Zwitserland", "year": "2008", "humanity": "5.7", "justiceSystem": "6.4", "police": "6.9", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "5.8", "politicalParties": "4.7", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.6", "ISO": "CHE", "fillKey": "4-6"}}, "2010": {"BEL": {"country": "Belgie", "year": "2010", "humanity": "5.0", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "6.0", "politicians": "3.9", "parliament": "4.5", "politicalParties": "3.9", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "BEL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "BGR": {"country": "Bulgarije", "year": "2010", "humanity": "3.5", "justiceSystem": "2.5", "police": "3.9", "politicians": "2.0", "parliament": "2.4", "politicalParties": "2.0", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "BGR", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "CYP": {"country": "Cyprus", "year": "2010", "humanity": "3.8", "justiceSystem": "5.6", "police": "5.5", "politicians": "3.6", "parliament": "4.6", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "4.4", "ISO": "CYP", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "DNK": {"country": "Denemarken", "year": "2010", "humanity": "6.8", "justiceSystem": "7.4", "police": "7.7", "politicians": "5.0", "parliament": "5.8", "politicalParties": "5.2", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.2", "ISO": "DNK", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "DEU": {"country": "Duitsland", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.7", "justiceSystem": "5.7", "police": "6.9", "politicians": "3.4", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "DEU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "EST": {"country": "Estland", "year": "2010", "humanity": "5.7", "justiceSystem": "5.2", "police": "6.2", "politicians": "3.6", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "5.2", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "EST", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "FIN": {"country": "Finland", "year": "2010", "humanity": "6.5", "justiceSystem": "6.9", "police": "8.0", "politicians": "4.4", "parliament": "5.4", "politicalParties": "4.5", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "6.6", "ISO": "FIN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "FRA": {"country": "Frankrijk", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.3", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "5.6", "politicians": "3.2", "parliament": "4.1", "politicalParties": "3.1", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "FRA", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GRC": {"country": "Griekenland", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.0", "justiceSystem": "3.8", "police": "4.6", "politicians": "1.4", "parliament": "2.0", "politicalParties": "1.4", "europeanParliament": "2.6", "un": "2.6", "ISO": "GRC", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "HUN": {"country": "Hongarije", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "4.6", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "3.1", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "3.1", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "HUN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "IRL": {"country": "Ierland", "year": "2010", "humanity": "5.3", "justiceSystem": "5.1", "police": "6.5", "politicians": "3.1", "parliament": "3.7", "politicalParties": "3.1", "europeanParliament": "4.1", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "IRL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ISL": {"country": "IJsland", "year": "2010", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "ISL", "fillKey": "none"}, "ITA": {"country": "Italie", "year": "2010", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "ITA", "fillKey": "none"}, "XKX": {"country": "Kosovo", "year": "2010", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "XKX", "fillKey": "none"}, "HRV": {"country": "Kroatie", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.6", "justiceSystem": "3.2", "police": "4.4", "politicians": "1.6", "parliament": "2.3", "politicalParties": "1.8", "europeanParliament": "3.3", "un": "3.9", "ISO": "HRV", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "LTU": {"country": "Litouwen", "year": "2010", "humanity": " ", "justiceSystem": " ", "police": " ", "politicians": " ", "parliament": " ", "politicalParties": " ", "europeanParliament": " ", "un": " ", "ISO": "LTU", "fillKey": "none"}, "NLD": {"country": "Nederland", "year": "2010", "humanity": "6.0", "justiceSystem": "5.9", "police": "6.3", "politicians": "5.2", "parliament": "5.4", "politicalParties": "5.3", "europeanParliament": "4.9", "un": "5.6", "ISO": "NLD", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "NOR": {"country": "Noorwegen", "year": "2010", "humanity": "6.7", "justiceSystem": "6.9", "police": "7.2", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "6.0", "politicalParties": "4.9", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.7", "ISO": "NOR", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "UKR": {"country": "Oekraine", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.2", "justiceSystem": "2.3", "police": "2.5", "politicians": "1.8", "parliament": "2.0", "politicalParties": "2.0", "europeanParliament": "4.0", "un": "4.0", "ISO": "UKR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "AUT": {"country": "Oostenrijk", "year": "2010", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "AUT", "fillKey": "none"}, "POL": {"country": "Polen", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.4", "justiceSystem": "4.3", "police": "5.4", "politicians": "2.7", "parliament": "3.4", "politicalParties": "2.5", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "POL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "PRT": {"country": "Portugal", "year": "2010", "humanity": "3.7", "justiceSystem": "3.5", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.0", "parliament": "2.9", "politicalParties": "2.0", "europeanParliament": "3.7", "un": "4.3", "ISO": "PRT", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "SVN": {"country": "Slovenie", "year": "2010", "humanity": "3.9", "justiceSystem": "3.1", "police": "5.0", "politicians": "2.3", "parliament": "3.0", "politicalParties": "2.2", "europeanParliament": "3.7", "un": "4.1", "ISO": "SVN", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "SVK": {"country": "Slowakije", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "3.5", "police": "4.5", "politicians": "2.8", "parliament": "3.2", "politicalParties": "2.7", "europeanParliament": "4.4", "un": "4.8", "ISO": "SVK", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ESP": {"country": "Spanje", "year": "2010", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "4.4", "police": "6.3", "politicians": "2.7", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "2.7", "europeanParliament": "4.5", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "ESP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "CZE": {"country": "Tsjechie", "year": "2010", "humanity": "4.6", "justiceSystem": "4.1", "police": "4.9", "politicians": "2.6", "parliament": "3.3", "politicalParties": "2.7", "europeanParliament": "4.1", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "CZE", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GBR": {"country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "year": "2010", "humanity": "5.4", "justiceSystem": "5.2", "police": "6.2", "politicians": "3.4", "parliament": "4.1", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "3.4", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "GBR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SWE": {"country": "Zweden", "year": "2010", "humanity": "6.3", "justiceSystem": "6.5", "police": "7.0", "politicians": "5.0", "parliament": "6.3", "politicalParties": "5.1", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.3", "ISO": "SWE", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "CHE": {"country": "Zwitserland", "year": "2010", "humanity": "5.6", "justiceSystem": "6.3", "police": "7.0", "politicians": "5.0", "parliament": "5.8", "politicalParties": "4.8", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "5.3", "ISO": "CHE", "fillKey": "4-6"}}, "2012": {"BEL": {"country": "Belgie", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "6.1", "politicians": "4.3", "parliament": "5.0", "politicalParties": "4.2", "europeanParliament": "5.1", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "BEL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "BGR": {"country": "Bulgarije", "year": "2012", "humanity": "3.4", "justiceSystem": "2.3", "police": "3.6", "politicians": "1.8", "parliament": "2.1", "politicalParties": "1.8", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "4.6", "ISO": "BGR", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "CYP": {"country": "Cyprus", "year": "2012", "humanity": "3.6", "justiceSystem": "4.7", "police": "4.9", "politicians": "2.5", "parliament": "3.4", "politicalParties": "2.4", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "3.7", "ISO": "CYP", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "DNK": {"country": "Denemarken", "year": "2012", "humanity": "7.0", "justiceSystem": "7.7", "police": "8.0", "politicians": "5.2", "parliament": "6.1", "politicalParties": "5.3", "europeanParliament": "5.2", "un": "6.6", "ISO": "DNK", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "DEU": {"country": "Duitsland", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.0", "justiceSystem": "6.0", "police": "6.9", "politicians": "3.8", "parliament": "4.9", "politicalParties": "3.8", "europeanParliament": "4.4", "un": "5.1", "ISO": "DEU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "EST": {"country": "Estland", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.5", "justiceSystem": "4.9", "police": "5.9", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "3.9", "politicalParties": "3.2", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "5.2", "ISO": "EST", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "FIN": {"country": "Finland", "year": "2012", "humanity": "6.6", "justiceSystem": "7.0", "police": "8.1", "politicians": "4.8", "parliament": "5.9", "politicalParties": "4.9", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.5", "ISO": "FIN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "FRA": {"country": "Frankrijk", "year": "2012", "humanity": "4.4", "justiceSystem": "5.0", "police": "5.9", "politicians": "3.2", "parliament": "4.1", "politicalParties": "3.1", "europeanParliament": "4.1", "un": "5.2", "ISO": "FRA", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GRC": {"country": "Griekenland", "year": "2012", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "GRC", "fillKey": "none"}, "HUN": {"country": "Hongarije", "year": "2012", "humanity": "4.8", "justiceSystem": "4.7", "police": "5.3", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "3.9", "politicalParties": "3.2", "europeanParliament": "4.2", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "HUN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "IRL": {"country": "Ierland", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.2", "justiceSystem": "5.2", "police": "6.6", "politicians": "3.1", "parliament": "3.6", "politicalParties": "3.0", "europeanParliament": "4.4", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "IRL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ISL": {"country": "IJsland", "year": "2012", "humanity": "6.0", "justiceSystem": "5.8", "police": "7.8", "politicians": "3.9", "parliament": "4.2", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "4.2", "un": "6.3", "ISO": "ISL", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "ITA": {"country": "Italie", "year": "2012", "humanity": "4.8", "justiceSystem": "4.5", "police": "6.1", "politicians": "2.0", "parliament": "3.2", "politicalParties": "2.0", "europeanParliament": "4.3", "un": "5.2", "ISO": "ITA", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "XKX": {"country": "Kosovo", "year": "2012", "humanity": "3.7", "justiceSystem": "3.2", "police": "5.6", "politicians": "2.1", "parliament": "3.1", "politicalParties": "2.3", "europeanParliament": "5.3", "un": "6.1", "ISO": "XKX", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "HRV": {"country": "Kroatie", "year": "2012", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "HRV", "fillKey": "none"}, "LTU": {"country": "Litouwen", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.2", "justiceSystem": "4.0", "police": "5.5", "politicians": "2.9", "parliament": "3.1", "politicalParties": "2.8", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "LTU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "NLD": {"country": "Nederland", "year": "2012", "humanity": "6.0", "justiceSystem": "6.1", "police": "6.4", "politicians": "5.1", "parliament": "5.3", "politicalParties": "5.1", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.7", "ISO": "NLD", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "NOR": {"country": "Noorwegen", "year": "2012", "humanity": "6.7", "justiceSystem": "7.2", "police": "7.2", "politicians": "5.1", "parliament": "6.3", "politicalParties": "5.2", "europeanParliament": "4.9", "un": "6.7", "ISO": "NOR", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "UKR": {"country": "Oekraine", "year": "2012", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "1.9", "police": "2.0", "politicians": "1.7", "parliament": "1.8", "politicalParties": "1.9", "europeanParliament": "3.9", "un": "3.9", "ISO": "UKR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "AUT": {"country": "Oostenrijk", "year": "2012", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "AUT", "fillKey": "none"}, "POL": {"country": "Polen", "year": "2012", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "3.7", "police": "5.3", "politicians": "2.2", "parliament": "3.0", "politicalParties": "2.2", "europeanParliament": "4.2", "un": "5.0", "ISO": "POL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "PRT": {"country": "Portugal", "year": "2012", "humanity": "3.6", "justiceSystem": "3.5", "police": "5.3", "politicians": "1.8", "parliament": "2.5", "politicalParties": "1.8", "europeanParliament": "3.2", "un": "4.1", "ISO": "PRT", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "SVN": {"country": "Slovenie", "year": "2012", "humanity": "4.6", "justiceSystem": "3.3", "police": "5.3", "politicians": "2.3", "parliament": "3.0", "politicalParties": "2.3", "europeanParliament": "3.8", "un": "4.2", "ISO": "SVN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SVK": {"country": "Slowakije", "year": "2012", "humanity": "3.8", "justiceSystem": "3.2", "police": "4.1", "politicians": "2.8", "parliament": "3.1", "politicalParties": "2.7", "europeanParliament": "3.7", "un": "4.2", "ISO": "SVK", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "ESP": {"country": "Spanje", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "3.7", "police": "5.9", "politicians": "1.9", "parliament": "3.4", "politicalParties": "1.9", "europeanParliament": "3.9", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "ESP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "CZE": {"country": "Tsjechie", "year": "2012", "humanity": "4.5", "justiceSystem": "4.1", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.6", "parliament": "3.2", "politicalParties": "2.7", "europeanParliament": "3.9", "un": "4.8", "ISO": "CZE", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GBR": {"country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.4", "justiceSystem": "5.6", "police": "6.6", "politicians": "3.7", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "3.7", "europeanParliament": "3.4", "un": "5.2", "ISO": "GBR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SWE": {"country": "Zweden", "year": "2012", "humanity": "6.0", "justiceSystem": "6.3", "police": "6.7", "politicians": "4.7", "parliament": "5.9", "politicalParties": "4.9", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "6.3", "ISO": "SWE", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "CHE": {"country": "Zwitserland", "year": "2012", "humanity": "5.7", "justiceSystem": "6.5", "police": "7.2", "politicians": "5.2", "parliament": "6.1", "politicalParties": "5.0", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "CHE", "fillKey": "4-6"}}, "2014*": {"BEL": {"country": "Belgie", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "5.0", "justiceSystem": "5.0", "police": "6.0", "politicians": "4.1", "parliament": "4.8", "politicalParties": "4.1", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.2", "ISO": "BEL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "BGR": {"country": "Bulgarije", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "BGR", "fillKey": "none"}, "CYP": {"country": "Cyprus", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "CYP", "fillKey": "none"}, "DNK": {"country": "Denemarken", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "6.9", "justiceSystem": "7.4", "police": "7.7", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "5.9", "politicalParties": "5.1", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "6.3", "ISO": "DNK", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "DEU": {"country": "Duitsland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "5.1", "justiceSystem": "5.2", "police": "6.7", "politicians": "3.1", "parliament": "3.6", "politicalParties": "2.9", "europeanParliament": "4.4", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "DEU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "EST": {"country": "Estland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "5.6", "justiceSystem": "5.2", "police": "6.1", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.4", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "4.4", "un": "4.7", "ISO": "EST", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "FIN": {"country": "Finland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "6.7", "justiceSystem": "6.8", "police": "7.9", "politicians": "4.6", "parliament": "5.6", "politicalParties": "4.7", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "6.2", "ISO": "FIN", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "FRA": {"country": "Frankrijk", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "FRA", "fillKey": "none"}, "GRC": {"country": "Griekenland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "GRC", "fillKey": "none"}, "HUN": {"country": "Hongarije", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "4.2", "justiceSystem": "4.6", "police": "5.3", "politicians": "2.9", "parliament": "3.8", "politicalParties": "3.0", "europeanParliament": "4.8", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "HUN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "IRL": {"country": "Ierland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "5.2", "justiceSystem": "5.3", "police": "6.3", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "3.8", "politicalParties": "3.3", "europeanParliament": "4.6", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "IRL", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "ISL": {"country": "IJsland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "ISL", "fillKey": "none"}, "ITA": {"country": "Italie", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "ITA", "fillKey": "none"}, "XKX": {"country": "Kosovo", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "XKX", "fillKey": "none"}, "HRV": {"country": "Kroatie", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "HRV", "fillKey": "none"}, "LTU": {"country": "Litouwen", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "4.9", "justiceSystem": "4.5", "police": "5.7", "politicians": "3.1", "parliament": "3.3", "politicalParties": "3.0", "europeanParliament": "5.2", "un": "5.6", "ISO": "LTU", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "NLD": {"country": "Nederland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "6.0", "justiceSystem": "6.0", "police": "6.4", "politicians": "4.9", "parliament": "5.2", "politicalParties": "4.9", "europeanParliament": "4.5", "un": "5.5", "ISO": "NLD", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "NOR": {"country": "Noorwegen", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "6.6", "justiceSystem": "7.2", "police": "7.4", "politicians": "5.3", "parliament": "6.7", "politicalParties": "5.3", "europeanParliament": "5.0", "un": "6.7", "ISO": "NOR", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "UKR": {"country": "Oekraine", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "UKR", "fillKey": "none"}, "AUT": {"country": "Oostenrijk", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "5.0", "justiceSystem": "5.7", "police": "6.5", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.7", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "3.6", "un": "4.4", "ISO": "AUT", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "POL": {"country": "Polen", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "3.9", "justiceSystem": "3.5", "police": "5.1", "politicians": "2.0", "parliament": "2.8", "politicalParties": "2.0", "europeanParliament": "3.6", "un": "4.6", "ISO": "POL", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "PRT": {"country": "Portugal", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "3.6", "justiceSystem": "3.7", "police": "5.6", "politicians": "2.0", "parliament": "3.1", "politicalParties": "2.2", "europeanParliament": "3.4", "un": "4.6", "ISO": "PRT", "fillKey": "2-4"}, "SVN": {"country": "Slovenie", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "4.1", "justiceSystem": "3.1", "police": "5.5", "politicians": "1.9", "parliament": "2.8", "politicalParties": "2.0", "europeanParliament": "3.4", "un": "4.2", "ISO": "SVN", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SVK": {"country": "Slowakije", "year": "2014*", "humanity": ".", "justiceSystem": ".", "police": ".", "politicians": ".", "parliament": ".", "politicalParties": ".", "europeanParliament": ".", "un": ".", "ISO": "SVK", "fillKey": "none"}, "ESP": {"country": "Spanje", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "4.8", "justiceSystem": "4.0", "police": "6.3", "politicians": "2.2", "parliament": "3.7", "politicalParties": "2.2", "europeanParliament": "3.8", "un": "4.8", "ISO": "ESP", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "CZE": {"country": "Tsjechie", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "4.6", "justiceSystem": "4.7", "police": "5.7", "politicians": "3.3", "parliament": "4.0", "politicalParties": "3.4", "europeanParliament": "4.2", "un": "4.8", "ISO": "CZE", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "GBR": {"country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "5.4", "justiceSystem": "5.6", "police": "6.3", "politicians": "3.5", "parliament": "4.3", "politicalParties": "3.5", "europeanParliament": "3.1", "un": "4.9", "ISO": "GBR", "fillKey": "4-6"}, "SWE": {"country": "Zweden", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "6.2", "justiceSystem": "6.4", "police": "6.9", "politicians": "5.0", "parliament": "6.2", "politicalParties": "5.1", "europeanParliament": "4.7", "un": "6.4", "ISO": "SWE", "fillKey": "6-8"}, "CHE": {"country": "Zwitserland", "year": "2014*", "humanity": "5.7", "justiceSystem": "6.6", "police": "7.2", "politicians": "5.2", "parliament": "6.2", "politicalParties": "5.1", "europeanParliament": "4.5", "un": "5.4", "ISO": "CHE", "fillKey": "4-6"}}}}